Daniel Yankelovich Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Organizations/Professional Services,1960-1992
  - William T. Grant Foundation Commission on Work, Family and Citizenship
    - Reports
      - George, Rosemary,, Youth Policies and Programs in Selected Countries, 1987 Aug (Box 71:1655)
      - The Forgotten Half: Pathways to Success for America's Youth and Young Families, Final Report of Commission, 1988 Nov (Box 71:1656)
      - The Forgotten Half: Non-College Youth in America: An Interim Report on the School-to-Work Transition (2 copies), 1988 Jan (Box 71:1657-1658)
      - Brochures on The Forgotten Half Reports, 1988 (Box 71:1659)
      - Howe II, Harold and Halperin, Samuel, statement before the U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1989 Jan 27 (Box 71:1660)
      - Wetzel, James R., American Youth: A Statistical Snapshot, 1987 Jun (Box 71:1661)
      - Youth and America's Future: charts, 1988 Sep (Box 71:1662)
    - Related Material for William T. Grant Foundation
      - Education Writers Association, First Jobs, 1990 (Box 71:1663)
      - Education Writers Association, Training for Work: What the U.S. Can Learn from Europe, 1990 (Box 71:1664)
      - Educational Testing Service, Policy Information Center, From School to Work, 1990 (Box 71:1665)
      - "The Forgotten Half": conference information, 1990 Jan 29-30 (Box 71:1666)
      - The Job Training and Basic Skills Act, 1990 (Box 71:1667)
      - Melaville, Atelia and Blank, Martin J., What it Takes: Structuring Interagency Partnerships to Connect Children and Families with Comprehensive Service, 1991 (Box 71:1668)
      - National Collaboration for Youth, Making the Grade: A Report Card on American Youth, 1990 Apr (Box 71:1669)
      - Northdurft, William E. and Jobs for the Future, Youth Apprenticeship, American Style, 1990 (Box 71:1670)
      - Nunn, Sam, Remarks at the Democratic Leadership Council Annual Conference, 1990 Mar 23 (Box 71:1671)
      - Outline of National and Community Service Act, 1990 (Box 71:1672)
      - Senate Bill 543, 1989 (Box 71:1673)
      - Youth Brief, [1988] (Box 71:1674)
  - WDY Consulting Group
    - Board of Directors meeting, 1988 Jan 27 (Box 71:1675)
    - Business plan, 1988 Jan 18 (Box 71:1676)
    - Clippings, undated, 1990 (Box 71:1677)
    - Correspondence, undated, 1987-1991 (Box 71:1678)
    - Integrated Strategies, Inc., 1988 (Box 71:1679)
    - Israel: questionnaire, 1990 Apr (Box 72:1680)
    - National Institute for Research Advancement (NIRA)
      - NIRA Publications, [1987] (Box 72:1681)
      - 1987 NIRA: pamphlet, 1987 (Box 72:1682)
      - Research Output - Agenda for Japan in the 1990s, 1988 (Box 72:1683)
    - Japan Center for International Exchange: pamphlet, 1987 (Box 72:1684)
    - New WSY products, [1987] (Box 72:1685)
    - Nishimoto, Keiko: interview with D. Yankelovich, 1989-1990 (Box 72:1686)
    - Oisi Conference "Social Change in Japan and the United States: Implications for Bilateral Relations, 1988 Dec 10-11
      - Agenda, 1988 (Box 72:1687-1688)
      - Iawao, Sumiko, "Recent Changes in Japanese Attitudes", 1988 (Box 72:1689)
      - Shimada, Haruo, "Japanese Corporate Culture: Lessons For Foreign Direct Investment", 1988 (Box 72:1690)
    - Presentations
      - "America in Post-Reagan Era" (in Japanese), undated (Box 72:1691)
    - Press release: WSY establishment, 1987 Mar 31 (Box 72:1692)
    - Quality inventory, 1991 (Box 72:1693)
    - Romberg, Alan D., The United States and Japan, Changing Societies in a Changing Relationship, 1987 (Box 72:1694)
  - Society for the Advancement of Socio-Economics (SASE)
    - Executive Council minutes, 1990 Mar 16 (Box 72:1695)
    - Second Annual International Conference on Socio-Economics, 1990 Mar 16-18 (Box 72:1696)
    - Nomination of D. Yankelovich as SASE President, 1990 Mar (Box 72:1697)
    - The Responsive Community: An Intellectual Quarterly (SASE journal), 1990-1991 (Box 72:1698)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 72:1699)
  - Strategies for a Global Economy, Inc. (SAGE)
    - (SEE ALSO: Boxes 97-98)
    - Globe Trends 1990 - draft, 1990 Feb 22 (Box 72:1700)
    - Globe Trends 1990 - draft, edited, 1990 Mar 12 (Box 72:1701)
    - Globe Trends 1990, 1990 (Box 72:1702)
    - Globe Trends 1990: working copy with notes, 1990 (Box 72:1703)
    - "Globe Trends 1990: Presentation of Services" (sales presentation), 1990 (Box 73:1704)
    - Globe Trends 1990 - Selected Excerpts, 1990 (Box 73:1705)
    - Globe Trends 1990 - Selected Excerpts - working copy with notes, 1990 (Box 73:1706)
    - Sales letters, 1990-1991 (Box 73:1707)
    - Sales outline - draft 3, 1990-1991 (Box 73:1708)
    - Globe Trends 1991
      - , [1991] (Box 73:1709)
      - Globe Trends 1991, editied (incomplete), [1991] (Box 73:1710)
    - IBM, 1991 (Box 73:1711)
    - "Lessons Learned in the U.S. Market" - draft, 1990 Mar 13 (Box 73:1712)
    - U.S.- Japan databook, 1988 (Box 73:1713)
    - Yamamoto Seminar, Japan: notes, 1988 Dec 12 (Box 73:1714)
    - WSY quality management program, 1991 (Box 73:1715)
  - Yankelovich, Skelly, and White, Inc.
    - Focus group session on world affairs: transcript, undated (Box 73:1716)
    - "The Mushiness Index: A Refinement in Public Policy Polling Techniques", 1981 Mar (Box 73:1717-1718)
    - Key Elements of the Public Policy Process: The Analytic Framework of Market Alert, undated (Box 73:1719)
    - Students and Drugs, 1975 (Box 73:1720)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Cigarette Smoking Among Teenagers and Young Women, [1977] (Box 73:1721)
- Series IV: Subject Files,1965-1992
  - Community
    - AT&T Management Sciences Division, Community Leaders Perception of Local Problems and National Issues, 1969 Jun (Box 74:1722)
    - AT&T Management Sciences Division, Community Leaders - Their Community Views and Participation, 1970 Oct (Box 74:1723)
  - Consumerism
    - Bauer, Raymond A., "Consumerism in Perspective": address, 1971 May (Box 74:1724)
    - Clippings, undated, 1971-1972 (Box 74:1725)
    - Heilbroner, Robert, "Counterrevolutionary America", 1967 (Box 74:1726)
  - Education
    - America 2000: An Education Strategy - sourcebook, 1991 (Box 74:1727)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum, America's Competitive Challenge, 1983 Apr (Box 74:1728)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education, Report to the National Taskforce on Higher Education and the Public Interest, 1987 Oct (Box 74:1729-1730)
    - Gallup, George, "Gallup Poll of the Public's Attitude Toward the Public Schools", Phi Delta Kappan, 1980 Sep (Box 74:1731)
    - Gentile, Claudia, Exploring New Methods for Collecting Students' School-Based Writing, 1992 Apr (Box 74:1732)
    - Heaviside, Sheila and Elizabeth Farris, Education Partnerships in Public Elementary and Secondary Schools, 1989 Feb (Box 74:1733)
    - Jones, J., M. Goertz and C. Kuh, eds., Minorities in Graduate Education: Pipeline, Policy, and Practice, 1992 (Box 74:1734)
    - Myers, James R. and Elizabeth Werner Scott, Getting Skilled, Getting Ahead, 1989 (Box 74:1735)
    - The National Science Board Commission on Pre-College Education in Mathematics, Science, and Technology, Educating For The 21st Century, [1984] (Box 74:1736)
    - National Task Force on Higher Education and the Public Interest: meeting proceedings, 1987 Nov 12 (Box 74:1737-1738)
    - National Task Force on Higher Education and the Public Interest: meeting proceedings, 1987 Nov 12 (Box 75:1739-1740)
    - Northdurft, William and Jobs for the Future, Youth, Apprenticeship, American Style: A Strategy for Expanding School and Career Opportunities - Conference Report, 1990 Dec (Box 75:1741)
    - Rasell, E. and L. Mishel, "Shortchanging Education", 1990 (Box 75:1742)
    - Sloan Commission on Government and Higher Education: report, 1980 (Box 75:1743-1744)
  - Energy
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Energy and the Future, 1973 (Box 75:1745)
    - Fuel & Energy Consultant, Inc., 1976 (Box 75:1746)
    - Spitzer, Robert, "Technological Aspects of the Quest for Energy Autochthony in the United States", 1977 (Box 75:1747)
    - Policy Perspectives, Protecting the Environment: Progress, Prospects, and the Public View, 1977 (Box 75:1747)
    - TIME, Inc. energy conference, 1977 (Box 75:1748)
    - YSW study concerning public reaction to President Carter's energy program, 1977 (Box 75:1749)
    - Netschert, Bruce, World Energy Resources in an Era of Rising Real Prices, 1979 (Box 75:1750)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, Nuclear Energy and International Cooperation: A Third World Perception of the Erosion of Confidence, 1979 (Box 75:1750)
    - The Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies: energy reports, 1980-1982 (Box 75:1751)
    - Mitre Corporation, U.S. Energy Strategies: Some Options for Eliminating Oil Imports, 1981 Apr (Box 75:1752)
    - Harvard University Workshop on Energy and Social Adaptation, 1981 May 21-23 (Box 75:1753-1755)
  - Family
    - Russell Sage Foundation, Indicators of Change in the American Family, 1970 (Box 75:1756)
    - Meredith Corporation, A Report on the American Family, 1972 (Box 76:1757)
    - Wattenberg, Ben, The Forming Families: The Spark in the Tinder 1975-1985, 1974 (Box 76:1758)
    - Monitor Conference, "The Family," sponsored by YSW, 1977 Nov 3-4 (Box 76:1758)
    - Daedalus journal edition on the family, 1977 Spring (Box 76:1759)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW) literature, 1979 (Box 76:1760)
    - Parents Without Partners literature, 1979 (Box 76:1761)
    - National Family Opinion, Inc. single parent study, 1979 (Box 76:1762)
    - American Family journal, 1981 Feb/Mar (Box 76:1762)
    - American Council of Life Insurance, The Shape of the American Family in the Year 2000, 1982 Fall (Box 76:1763)
  - Health Care
    - Ellwood, Paul and Lynn Etheredge, "The 21st Century American Health System: Overview and Accountable Health Partnerships", 1991 Sep 3 (Box 76:1764)
    - California Department of Insurance, "California Health Care in the 21st Century: A Vision for Reform", 1992 (Box 76:1765)
    - Conservative Democratic Forum Health Package, 1992 Sep (Box 76:1766)
    - Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1993 (Box 76:1766)
    - Analysis Group Inc., "Managed Competition: An Economist's Perspective", 1993 (Box 76:1767)
    - Preliminary memorandum for the U.S. Interagency Task Force, 1993 (Box 76:1768)
    - Arthur D. Little, Inc., Health Care Cost Reduction: The InterLATA Component, 1993 (Box 76:1769-1770)
    - Arthur D. Little, Inc., "Telecommunications: Can It Help Solve America's Health Care Problems", 1992 Jul (Box 76:1771-1772)
  - Human Rights
    - Amnesty International, Report on Torture, 1975 (Box 76:1773)
    - Manning, Bayless, "Goals, Ideology and Foreign Policy", [1975] (Box 76:1774)
    - Institute for World Order, Inc., 1976 (Box 76:1774)
    - Butler, William and Georges Levasseur, Human Rights and the Legal System in Iran, 1976 Mar (Box 76:1775)
    - Sutton, Francis, "Human Rights, Freedom and the Liberal Tradition", 1976 Oct 19 (Box 77:1776)
    - Soedjatmoko, J. E., "Peace, Security and Human Dignity in Asia", 1976 Nov 24 (Box 77:1776)
    - Cleveland, Harlan, "Peace and Human Rights," chapter 9 of The Obligations of Power, 1976 Dec 30 (Box 77:1777)
    - Shulman, Marshall, "On Learning To Live With Authoritarian Regimes," in Foreign Affairs, 1977 Jan (Box 77:1777)
    - Zonis, Marvin, "Human Rights and American Foreign Policy: The Case of Iran", 1977 Mar (Box 77:1778)
    - Amnesty International, Matchbox, 1977 Winter (Box 77:1778)
  - Inflation
    - Friedman, Irving
      - "Recovery and Growth Without Inflation", 1976 Jun 17 (Box 77:1779)
      - "To What Extent Have Inflationary Trends in the World Economy Been Conquered?", 1979 Feb (Box 77:1779)
      - "Global Aspects of Inflation", 1979 May 10 (Box 77:1780)
      - "Democracy and Persistent Inflation", 1979 (Box 77:1780)
      - "A New Approach to Inflation", 1979 Jun 21 (Box 77:1781)
      - "The Outlook for the World Economy", 1980 (Box 77:1781)
      - Draft of article concerning inflation, 1980 Sep (Box 77:1782)
    - Sawhill, Isabel, "The Political Economy of Inflation and Unemployment", 1980 Jan (Box 77:1783)
    - Mettler, Ruben, "Strategy for a Strong Economy: Building a New American Political Consensus", 1980 Apr 28 (Box 77:1783)
    - Hoadley, Walter (ed.), The Economy and the President: 1980 and Beyond (including chapter by D. Yankelovich), 1980 Mar (Box 77:1784-1785)
    - Slater, Joseph, "Energy: A Challenge to Governance", 1980 Apr 9 (Box 77:1786)
    - Kaufman, Henry, "America's Economic and Financial Dilemma", 1980 (Box 77:1786)
    - Committee for Economic Development (CED)
      - Fighting Inflation and Rebuilding a Strong Economy, 1980 Sep (Box 77:1787)
      - American Assembly, Economic Issues and the President: 1980 and Beyond - draft, 1980 Mar (Box 77:1788)
      - Freund, William and Paul Manchester, "Productivity and Inflation", 1980 Apr 22 (Box 77:1788)
      - Committees and resolutions, 1980 (Box 77:1789)
      - Annual report, Addressing the Crucial Issues, 1979 (Box 77:1790)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1980 Mar 31 (Box 77:1790)
      - Task Force on Inflation, 1980 Mar-May (Box 77:1791-1793)
      - Transnational Corporations and Third World Development: Increasing the Mutual Gains - draft, 1980 May 15 (Box 77:1794)
      - Looking Ahead: Crucial Economic Issues For Business and Society in the 198, 1980 May 15 (Box 77:1795)
  - Japan
    - YSW study, Meeting Japan's Challenge: The Need For Leadership, 1982 (Box 77:1796)
    - Brookings Institution and NIRA, The Future Course of U.S.-Japan Relations, 1983 (Box 77:1796)
    - Aoki, Masahiko, "The Japanese Bureaucracy in Economic Administration: A Rational Regulator or Pluralist Agent?", 1986 (Box 78:1797)
    - National Science Foundation, The Science and Technology Resources of Japan: A Comparison With the United States, 1988 (Box 78:1797)
    - Iwao, Sumiko, "Recent Changes in Japanese Attitudes", 1988 (Box 78:1798)
    - Aoki, Masahiko, "Horizontal vs. Vertical Information Structure of the Firm: An Approach to U.S. - Japan Comparison of Industrial Organization", 1988 (Box 78:1798)
    - United States-Japan Foundation, Forum, 1988 Fall (Box 78:1799)
    - Yakushiji, Taizo, "Political Constraints For Policy Making in Japan: The Grafted Democracy and New Political Recruits", 1988 (Box 78:1799)
    - Shimada, Hiruo, "Japanese Corporate Culture: Lessons From Foreign Direct Investment", 1988 (Box 78:1800)
    - Oiso Conference on Social Change in Japan and the United States: Implications for the Bilateral Relationship, 1988 Dec 10-11 (Box 78:1801)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 78:1802)
    - Romberg, Alan, "The Future of U.S.-Japan Relations," Council Briefings (Council of U.S. Foreign Relations), 1989 Feb (Box 78:1803)
    - Daedalus, Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1900 Summer (Box 78:1804)
    - Ohira Memorial Lecture Series, address by Jimmy Carter, 1990 (Box 78:1805)
    - "World Economy in the 1990s: A Japanese Central Banker's View," address by Yasushi Mineo, 1990 (Box 78:1805)
    - Stokes, Bruce, The Inevitability of Managed Trade: The Future Strategic Trade Policy Debate, 1990 (Box 78:1806)
    - White, Merry, Challenging Tradition: Women in Japan, 1991 (Box 78:1806)
  - Ladd, Everett Carl: writings
    - "The American Idea of Nation - 1985", [1985] (Box 78:1807)
    - "The American Party System Today: 'The disadvantage of being inapplicable...to the society'", 1977 (Box 78:1808)
    - "The American 'Sense of Nation', 1981", 1981 (Box 78:1809)
    - "The Brittle Mandate: Electoral Dealignment and the 1980 Presidential Election", 1981 (Box 78:1810)
    - "An Essay on the 'End of Ideology'", 1982 (Box 78:1811)
    - "Examining the American Idea of Nation", 1985 (Box 78:1812)
    - "The GOP Revival of the '80s Continues", 1987 (Box 78:1813)
    - "Governing America: The Search for an Appropriate Vision", 1984 (Box 78:1814)
    - "On Mandates and Realignments: Understanding the 1984 Presidential Election", 1984 (Box 78:1815)
    - "Public Attitudes Toward Policy and Governance: Searching for the Sources and Meaning of 'The Reagan Revolution'", 1983 (Box 78:1816)
    - "Pursuing the New Class: Social Theory and Survey Data", 1978 (Box 78:1817)
    - "What Do Americans Really Think About the Environment?", 1990 (Box 78:1818)
  - Media
    - Association of National Advertisers, Management Viewpoints and Advertising Opportunities, 1962 (Box 78:1819)
    - American Marketing Association, conference proceedings, 1964 (Box 79:1820)
    - American Association of Advertising Agencies, The New A.A.A.A. Research on Consumer Judgement of Advertising: Background and Scope, 1964 (Box 79:1821)
    - Bureau of Advertising, Research Studies and Reports Published By Newspapers in the United States, 1964 (Box 79:1822)
    - Wells, William, "Consumers' Reactions to Advertisements: Some New Dimensions", [1965] (Box 79:1823)
    - W. R. Simmons & Associates study on media audiences, 1965 (Box 79:1824)
    - Trendex, Inc., "Proposal For a Quarterly National Radio Audience Measurement Report", 1965 (Box 79:1824)
    - University of Missouri Bulletin, "100 Books on Advertising" (8th ed.), 1965 (Box 79:1825)
    - Trendex, Inc. study on color television, 1965 (Box 79:1825)
    - Daniel & Charles, Inc., "The Top Twenty-Five" Media-Market Planning Guide, 1967 (Box 79:1826)
    - Roper Research Associates, Emerging Profiles of Television and Other Mass Media: Public Attitudes 1959-1967, 1967 (Box 79:1826)
    - Klapper, Joseph, "The Effects of Mass-Media-Depicted Violence: A Review of Research Findings", 1968 (Box 79:1827)
    - Study concerning mass media impact on voters, 1972, 1976 (Box 79:1828-1831)
    - NBC Corporate Planning, Broadcasting: The Next Ten Years, 1976 (Box 79:1832-1833)
    - Banks, Louis, "Living in a Newsocracy: All the News All the Time", 1980 (Box 79:1834)
    - Rice, Michael, "Playing at Producer or Editor -- An Exercise in Expanding the Mass Media's Treatment of Complex Issues", 1981 (Box 79:1834)
    - Washington Post and YSW, A Study of the Impact of Janet Cooke's Hoax Story, "Jimmy's World," on the Reputation and Standing of the Washington Post, 1981 (Box 79:1835-1836)
    - Aspen Institute Berlin, Mass Media and the Public: Europe and the United States, 1982 (Box 79:1837)
    - Schudson, Michael, The News Media and the Democratic Process, 1983 (Box 79:1837)
    - Roper Organization reports on public attitudes towards the media, 1984 (Box 79:1838)
    - Proposed study on the VCR and its entertainment impact, 1985 (Box 79:1839)
  - Methodology (polling)
    - Katz, Alvin, "Talking & Listening: Observations of a Group Interviewer", 1964 (Box 79:1840)
    - Katz, Alvin, "On Focus: The Group Interview in Market Research", 1964 (Box 79:1840)
    - London School of Economics and Political Science, A Study of the Effects of Reversing the Order of Presentation of Verbal Rating Scales, 1965 (Box 79:1841)
    - Tolley, B. Stuart, "A Basic Framework for the Analysis of Exploratory Attitude Research", 1965 (Box 79:1841)
    - Cohen, Jacob, "A Method of Market Segmentation Based on Multivariate Analysis of Attitude Data" - abstract, 1966 (Box 79:1842)
    - Weiss, Robert, "Issues in Holistic Research", 1967 (Box 79:1842)
    - Cohen, Jacob, "Segmentation in Consumer and Public Opinion Research" - abstract, 1967 (Box 80:1843)
    - Cohen, Jacob, "Multiple Regression as a General Data-Analytic System", 1967 (Box 80:1843)
    - London School of Economics and Political Science lecture series, 1959-1967 (Box 80:1844)
    - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., "Master Probability Sample Plan", undated (Box 80:1845)
  - Politics and government
    - Anderson, John B., "New Liberalism": address, 1980 (Box 80:1846)
    - Carter, Lisle C., "Power to the People: New Revolution or Political Piety": book chapter, undated (Box 80:1847)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. - articles, 1979-1980 (Box 80:1848)
    - Etzioni, Amitai, "Democrats in Support of the Public Interest: A Thematic Paper" - draft, 1982 Mar (Box 80:1849)
    - Hibbs, Douglas A., "President Reagan's Mandate From the 1980 Election: A Shift to the Right?", 1981 Sep (Box 80:1850)
    - Institute of Politics, John F. Kennedy School of Government, The Presidential Nominating System: A Primer, 1979 (Box 80:1851)
    - Kateb, George, "The Political Thought of Herbert Marcuse", 1969 (Box 80:1852)
    - Center for Political Research, National Journal, vol. 3, no. 33, 1971 Aug 14 (Box 80:1853)
    - Neoliberal conference sponsored by The Washington Monthly, 1983 Oct 21-23 (Box 80:1854)
    - Peters, Charles, "A Neoliberal's Manifesto," The Washington Monthly, 1983 May (Box 80:1855)
    - Public opinion statistics on Reagan presidency, 1985 (Box 80:1856)
    - Radio transcripts concerning 1984 presidential campaign, 1984 (Box 80:1857)
    - Vice-president Walter F. Mondale speech, 1980 Oct 23 (Box 80:1858)
    - de Segonzac, Adalbert, "French Admiration for Reagan Strong", 1981 (Box 80:1859)
    - Shaw, John, "Reagan Gets Mixed Reviews in Australia", 1981 (Box 80:1860)
    - "What Democrats are Missing; A New Explanation" - draft, 1982 Jan (Box 80:1861)
    - "Whittington, Less, "Canadians Still Reserve Judgment on Reagan", 1981 (Box 80:1862)
  - Polls
    - Bower, B., "The Power of Polls," Readers Digest, 1988 Jul (Box 80:1863)
    - Harris Survey - Indexes, 1974-1977 (Box 80:1864)
    - Harris Survey, 1975-1977 (Box 80:1865-1869)
    - Harris Survey, 1981-1985 (Box 81:1870-1873)
    - Harris Survey and Business Week/Harris Poll Indexes, 1983-1984, 1986-1988 (Box 81:1874)
    - Harris Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 81:1875-1878)
    - Harris Poll, 1988-1989 (Box 81:1879-1881)
    - Business Week/Harris Poll, undated, 1984-1988 (Box 81:1882-1886)
  - Presidential Campaigns
    - Notes and poll data, 1972 (Box 81:1887)
    - Columbia Journalism Review, "Election '72: How Fair?", 1973 Jan/Feb (Box 82:1888)
    - Common Cause literature on candidates' issue positions, 1975 (Box 82:1889-1893)
    - Van Deerlin, Rep. Lionel, "The Politics of Negativism," Congressional Record, 1975 Jun 12 (Box 82:1894)
    - NBC News poll, 1975 Nov 6 (Box 82:1895)
    - TIME/Yankelovich post-Florida primary survey, 1976 Mar 18 (Box 82:1896)
    - Lipset, Seymour, "Is Carter Sure to Win?", 1976 Aug (Box 82:1897)
    - Ladd, Everett Carl, "Class, Voting, and Ideology: The Inversion of the New Deal Order",, 1976 Aug (Box 82:1898)
    - Yankelovich, D., "Voter Apathy?" (with notes), 1976 (Box 82:1899)
    - Birnbaum, Norman, "The Presidential Election: The Last Phase", 1976 (Box 82:1900)
    - Menes, Bonnie, "A Cultural History of the American Nuclear Age: Have Americans Learned to Love the Bomb?", 1983 Nov 8 (Box 82:1901)
    - TIME/Yankelovich Poll, 1984 Feb 20 (Box 82:1902)
    - Public Agenda Foundation, Towards Public Judgment on the Nuclear Defense Issue: Phase I, Preparation of the Presidential Candidates' Briefing Books and the National Survey, 1984 Mar (Box 82:1903)
    - Public Agenda Foundation, Voter Options on Nuclear Arms Policy: A Briefing Book for the 1984 Elections (2 copies), 1984 (Box 82:1904-1905)
    - Notes for nuclear issue briefing book, 1984 (Box 82:1906)
    - Proposed revisions to Voter Options on Nuclear Arms Policy, 1984 (Box 82:1907)
    - Publicity for Voter Options on Nuclear Arms Policy, 1984 (Box 82:1908)
    - Ladd, Everett Carl, "Is Election '84 Really a Class Struggle?", 1984 Apr 30 (Box 82:1909)
    - NBC News Poll, 1984 (Box 82:1910)
    - ABC News/Washington Post Poll, 1984 (Box 82:1911)
    - Los Angeles Times Poll, 1984 (Box 82:1912)
    - National Public Radio poll by Louis Harris & Associates, Inc., 1984 (Box 83:1913)
    - Material on the gender gap and blue collar voting patterns, 1984 (Box 83:1914)
    - NBC News General Election Poll, 1984 Nov (Box 83:1915)
  - Public Opinion (International)